TUTOR: DR. LAM PHAM

GitHub (link); Linkedin (link); Google Scholar (link) lamd.pham22@gmail.com (Vienna, Austria)

MOTIVATION FOR THE PRACTICAL ML & DL COURSE

Nearly 15-year experience working on wide range of domains and different technologies (VLSI Design, DSP, Embedded System, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, etc.) motivates to share my knowledge. Hope that my course can be beneficial and help to build up your career path, especially in AI domain.

EDUCATION

University of Kent, UK

July 2020

PhD Fellow in Computer Science

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology, Vietnam

September 2012

MSc in Electrical & Electronic Engineering

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology, Vietnam

March 2009

Bachelor in Electronics & Telecommunication Engineering

KAGGLE COMPETITIONS

- Top-one team of IEEE BioCAS 2023 on Respiratory Sound Classification (link)
- Top-eight accuracy of DCASE-2023 Task 1 Challenge (link)
- Top-four accuracy of DCASE-2022 Task 1 Challenge (link)
- Top-seven accuracy ranking of DCASE-2021 Task 1A Challenge (link)
- Top-five accuracy of DCASE-2021 Task 1B Challenge (link)
- Top-six team ranking of DCASE-2020 Task 3 Challenge (link)
- Top-five team ranking of DCASE-2019 Task 1B Challenge (link)

EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist February 2021 - Present
DSAI, Austrian Institute of Technology (AIT)
Austria

Postdoctoral researcher

CVSSP, University of Surrey

August 2020 - January 2021

UK

PhD Fellow
School of Computing, University of Kent

November 2017 - July 2020

UK

Lecturer March 2013 - October 2017 Ho Chi Minh University of Technology Vietnam

Software Engineer March 2010 - February 2013
Renesas Electronics Corp. Vietnam

Software Engineer

Synopsys Corp.

June 2009 - February 2010

Vietnam

Software Engineer Intern

Intel - Altera Corp.

January 2009 - May 2010

Vietnam